At first glance, leverage looks awesome because if we take enough short positions,
乍一看 加杠杆很有用 因为如果我们有足够的空头头寸
we could technically have enough cash to pay for all of our long positions.
我们就有足够的现金支付所有多头头寸
But does this mean that more leverage is always better?
那么杠杆越高就越好吗？
Unfortunately, the answer is no.
遗憾的是 答案是否定的
If the stock price went down 10 percent,
如果股价下跌 10%
then our leveraged position would go down 20 percent,
那么加了杠杆的头寸将下降 20%
which is greater than the loss we'd incur without leverage.
比没有杠杆的下降幅度要大
So, as the saying goes,
俗话说得好
there's no such thing as a free lunch.
天下没有免费的午餐
Which means that the benefits of leverage come at a cost.
因此杠杆是个双刃剑
Using leverage can increase
利用杠杆能够
our potential gain but can also increase our potential losses.
提高潜在利得 但是也会增加潜在损失
A useful measure of the amount of leverage in a portfolio is the leverage ratio.
投资组合杠杆金额的衡量方式是杠杆比率
In terms of dollars,
用美元计算的话
if we added up the magnitudes of the long and short positions,
将做多和做空头寸的大小相加
and divided that sum by the notional,
然后除以名义价值
this would be the leverage ratio.
就等于杠杆比率
For example, if a portfolio had a notional or initial capital
例如 如果投资组合的名义价值或初始资本为 100 万美元
of $1 million and had $1 million in long positions,
做多头寸是 100 万美元
the leverage ratio would be one.
那么杠杆比率是 1
If the portfolio had the same notional of
如果投资组合的名义价值还是 100 万美元
1 million but borrowed cash to go long two million positions,
但是通过借贷现金做多 200 万
its leverage ratio would be two million divided by one million or two.
杠杆比率是 200 万除以 100 万 等于 2
If the portfolio had long positions totaling
如果投资组合的做多头寸为 100 万美元
$1 million and short positions also totaling $1 million,
做空头寸也是 100 万美元
then the leverage ratio would also be two million divided by one million, which is two.
那么杠杆比率还是 200 万除以 100 万 等于 2
If the longs were two million and the shorts were two million,
如果做多头寸为 200 万 做空头寸为 200 万
then the leverage ratio would be four.
那么杠杆比率为 4
So, I hope you noticed that the more positions we take
相对于初始资本来说
and absolute magnitude relative to the initial capital,
建立的头寸绝对值越大
the higher the leverage ratio.
杠杆比率就越高
For theoretical portfolio, that's used for analyzing a factor,
对于分析因子的理论投资组合来说
we assume a $1 notional.
我们假设名义价值为 1 美元
We add up the sum of the absolute values of the weights,
将权重的绝对值相加
then divide by the $1 notional to calculate the leverage ratio.
然后除以 1 美元名义价值 得出杠杆比率
Dividing by one doesn't change the sum.
除以 1 不会改变和的大小
So, we can skip the division.
所以可以跳过相除的步骤
For example, if we had three stocks in the portfolio with weights of negative 0.5,
例如 假设投资组合中有三支股票
positive 0.3, and positive 0.2,
权重分别为 -0.5 0.3 和 0.2
the sum of their absolute values is one.
绝对值之和为 1
So, the leverage ratio is also one.
所以杠杆比率也为 1
If on the other hand,
如果投资组合的权重
the portfolio had weights of negative one,
分别为 -1
positive 0.6, and positive 0.4,
0.6 和 0.4
then the sum of their absolute values is two.
那么绝对值之和为 2
So, the leverage ratio is also two.
所以杠杆比率也为 2
Let's revisit our goal,
再回到我们的目标
which was to rescale portfolio weights,
即重新调整投资组合的权重
so that we have a leverage ratio of one.
使杠杆比率为 1
To do this, we can sum up the absolute values of
我们将权重的绝对值相加
the weights and divide each of our original weights by this sum.
然后使每个原始权重除以这个和
By doing this division,
相除后
we are re-scaling the factor values so that the sum of their magnitudes equals one.
我们重新调整了因子值 使大小之和等于 1